Inventory of the Gordon Leo McDonough papers 0366
USC Libraries Special Collections
- Miscellaneous
  - MISCELLANEOUS materials in folders maps, 1933-1944
    - RECALL City election returns per precincts, 1938
    - REGISTERED VOTERS 2nd supervisorial district, June 1941
    - REGISTERED VOTERS 2nd supervisorial district, March 1942
    - REGISTERED VOTERS Board of Supervisors ex-officio elections I 942
      by: congressional supervisorial district
    - RESULTS OF OFFICIAL CANVAS primary election, 1938
    - RESULTS OF OFFICIAL CANVAS primary election members County Central Committes, 1940
    - SUPERVISORIAL CAMPAIGN correspondance, 1934 '53
    - UN-OFFICIA LIST OF CANDIDATES for office Primary election, August 1942
    - VOTES CAST 2nd Supervisorial district, MAY 1936
    - WILLARD HARPER lists of sponsors, 1940
    - UNMARKER (2 folies) A Lists of: field deputees 2nd supervisorial district, mailing, political contacts, [UNK] [UNK] official canvas primary election, 1938-'43 1942
    - UNMARKER (illegable) B, 1936
    - CAMPAIGN FOR MAYOR C correspondance, 1937
    - PRIMARY FINAL PRECINTS CARRIED [UNK], 19??
  - MISCELLANEOUS materials in folders enveloppes, 1934-1944
    - CAMPAIGN, 1944 (Box 93)
    - CAMPAIGN CORRESPONDANCE, 1944 '40
    - DINNER BOOSTER CLUB, 1944
    - ENDORSEMENTS, 1934 '33
    - ENDORSEMENTS, 1936
    - G L M PERSONAL, 1937
    - GOVERNER ROLPH'S LETTERS, 1934 '33 '27 '27
    - LIST OF PERSONS who circulated PETITIONS, 1936- 39
    - NEWSPAPER CLIPPINGS, 1940
    - REG. VOTERS, 1938 '36
    - LOCATION OF SIGNS Campaigns), 1934 '36 '37 '40; I folder
    - SPONSORS-ENDORSEMENTS, 1934
    - SPONSORS-ENDORSEMENTS, 1937
    - SPONSORS-ENDORSEMENTS, 1940
    - SPONSORS, 1936
    - VOLUNTEERS, 1939 '36 '37 '40
    - VOTE AUGUST primary election returns per precints 2nd District tabulations, 1936
  - Heading A thr V, 1935-1948
    - O P A GASOLINE Alpha-Ray therapy, American Hospital Organization Buffalo, increased Nego population, gasoline for government officials L A housing, McDonough junket trip, National Houding Authorty- McDonough report., 1943 (Box 94)
    - TRAFFIC MATTERS, 1935 ' 36 '37
      California Safety Council, contest Santa Fe - Southern Pacific Pacific Greyhound lines S F L A S Diego, for patrons only signs, L S [UNK] in 2nd supervisorial districts - resurfing 1938 listing, loading zones, pamphlet highway murder, parking ordinances, pedestrian lanes slow signs, suggested auto accident program, Strauss yielding highway barriers, stop signs, traffic safety program-California Safety Council, traffic laws reform, traffic situation in L A county.
    - AKER BILL Veterans cases, 1947
    - FORIGN AID DOMESTIC LEGISL. - TRUMAN PLAN HR 4840 ECONOMY, 1947 '48
      Fats oil industy-OPA ceilings, Foreign Assistance Act '48 government competition in export, governmental control of private enterprise, inclusion of Spain in European Recover Program, Marshall plan, prevent premature publication/radio announcement, U S machinery shipments to U S S R.
    - GAMBLING LEGISLATION HR 879 Bribary in interstate atletic competion., 1946 '47
    - FEDERAL CREDIT UNION LEGISL. 80 Congress 2nd Session HR2385 3327 Amend Fedral Credit Union Act, tranfer from jurisdiction of Fedral Deposit Insurance Corporation., 1947-48
    - PENSION LEGISLATION MISC, S715 F B I pensions, 1947
    - RESUME OF 80 Congress I Special 2n Regular Sessions Legislation summarized by catagories.
    - VETERANS CASES, July 1948
    - folder 2: H RES 99 LETTERS Communism communists in U S, Communist party of California, define communism outlaw, pamphlet Can American [UNK] the Communists?, Winston Churchill's Communism., 1947
    - un-used enveloppes headers
  - MISCELLANEOUS, 1935-1949
    material in folders with heading(s) A-B, C-U, S-U
    arranged alphabeticaaly by HEADING
    - BOY SCOUTS Boy Scouts of America, fees boat permit Puddinstone Reservoir., 1943 (Box 95)
    - CHURCH MATTERS Catholic Women's Clubs, intolerance (radio address),list of Cathlic churches,medical services to Parochial schools,Society of St. Vincent de Paul., 1935-43
    - GEO PAINE Fr.ORTER, 1942
    - REHABILITATION, 1938 '39
      Angora rabbits project,commodity compensation for county [UNK] for overtime work, co-operatives in California,manuel of information about department of Rehabilitation of county of L A,problems of rehabilitation in L A county,removal of indigents of County relief rolls,rotating men weed burning [UNK] sales of commodities produced by dept of Rehabiltation, Self-help stores, script issue, use of County owned loys for building purposes, manual weed abatement crews, weed tax, weed removal project
      Food stuff dispensaries, lay-offs in Dept. of Rehabilitation
    - RE WAIVE RECRUTING, 1943
    - SOLDIERS LETTERS MISC, 1943 '44
      County employees in military service, County of L A Board of Supervisors, letter to County employees in Armed Forces, military service record county employees, supervisorial [UNK] map, V mail letters.
    - Newspaper clippings WOOD, 1942
    - US CONGRESSMEN ET AL HR 1057 1674 3018 8279 9256 4142 S 659 1287 HJR 89 Additional salvafe collection, Alondra Park, civilian employees construction Panama Canal, Federal Housing Administration, foof stamp plan L A county, Los Angeles River Freeway, national employ-physically handicapped week-, physically handicapped problem- Voorhis remarks-, termination of war [UNK], un-employment condition L A county, W P A quota's. Aid for the aged, Defance Plant Corporatuons- disposal of equipment machinery, Franklin Delano Rooseveldt Park Project problem of transient people, provide for refendum on war, State Federal T B subsidaries, W P A projects., 1938-44
  - MISCELLANEOUS, 1935-1948
    material in folders enveloppes with headings C thr U arranged alphabetically by HEADING
    - CALIFORNIA SOUTHERN EMPIRE, 1943 '44 (Box 95)
      Alien Land Law, County Supervisors Association of California, County Supervisors California's Southern Emre, minutes of meetings County Supervisors of California Southen Empire '43, officers members of California' Southern Empire, prohibit use of Japanese language in schools, roster of supervisors by county.
    - CIVIC CENTER
      American Institute of Architects, Civic Center Report [UNK] county surveyors's report appraisal of portion of Civic Center, new County Court House, proceedings Board of Supervisors, [UNK] bond campaign for administrative trade center in L A county.
    - GRAND JURY
      Civic Committee letters to Grand Jury '41, final report L A county Grand Jury '37, 41, 42, Index to L A County final report '38.
    - HEALTH DEPARTMENT
      Investigation of repatriation of Mexican aliens '38.
    - L A WAR COUNCIL, 1943
      Civilian protection war services, index of war films [UNK] war use, L A County Defense Council, L A County civilan defence organisation, L A County fire department, [UNK] of meetings L A War Council '43, minutes of monthly meetin August, selection/appountments/resignations of officers Area War Councils, State of California War Council manual '43.
    - MEMO'S RE WORLD'S FAIR COMMITTEE International House at Mines Airfield., 1943 '44
    - MINUTES OF 26th annual CONVENTION of COUNTY SUPERVISORSS ASSOCIATION OF CALIFORNIA, 1936
    - PIN MARBLES GAMES, 1942 '43
      Amendment to license ordinance Pinn-Ball macines-proceedings report, Board of Supervisors, Office of City Council, ordinance 420I, Treasury Dept.-federal licenses.
    - POST WAR PLANNING Address McDonough meeting of achitects, post-war [UNK], post-war program L A county., 1943
    - PRODUCTION FOR USE Production for econimy plan.
    - TAX MATTERS County tax rate, reduction of taxes., 1944
    - THANK YOU LETTERS L A County council, L A County Fire Dept. employees's Union, Roads to Romance organization, zoning [UNK]-Miramonte districts, 1944
    - U S MARINE HOSPITAL COMMITTEE HR 3530 Lists of members, resolution proposed
    - UN-MARKED FOLDER A, 1939 '40 '41
      American Legion,Assembly California Legislature, county ordinance 3385, Fleet Reserve Association,L A County Council,national defence week,regular veterans organisation,salary reduction county employees on pensions, Teddy Rough Riders, unites Spanish War veterans, united veterans council, veterans credit organization.
    - B Central Gardens zoning matter, dicrimination,old age pensions, segregation,Women's political study club., 1937-44
  - MISCELLANEOUS, 1944-1962
    materials in folders
    arr. alphabetically by HEADING
    not analyzed by subject(s) organisation(s)
    - CAMPAIGN HR 3745 4222 9531 9582 5065 6376 8031 10788 11970 11990 11222, 1962 '61 (Box 96)
      (see Box folder contents)
    - CONGRATULATIONS, 1944
    - LETTERS RE 15th District HR4715 S 1882, 1944
    - POLITICAL Analyses of 1946 election
    - PRECINCT VOTING LIST OF PRIMARIES, 1946
    - THANKS FILE HR 2232 3755 S 101, 1945 '46
      Coalition Repub;icans anti New Deal Democrats in the South, food situation in L A county, L A Turf Club,racial discrimination, State Board of Equalization.
    - H J RES 325, 1952 '51 '53
      HR 130 2550 5080 6393 H J RES 57 325 Bricker resolution 130
    - REPRESENTATIVE G McDONOUGH Com. on Banking Currency
    - UNMARKED FOLIO Information by subjects
  - MISCELLANEOUS I-Q, 1953-1958
    in manilla enveloppes folders
    Arr. alphabetically by HEADINGS
    - I AM THE U S letter (Box 97)
    - McDONOUGH COLUMN involvement in legislation (see folder), 1953
    - POLISH AFFAIRS, 1958 '57 '55
      Investigation of Communist seizure of Poland HR 438, national commemoration in Congress, Polish American Congress, Polish Constituion Day 1791, Polish Claim Program, Polish struggle for feedam pamphlet - history of Poland.
      Polish Army veterans organization of America, Congressional Record Polish Constition Day.
    - TIME ARTICLE FILE Controversy Mc Donough - Congressional quarterly news service.
    - QUESTIONAIRE FORMS 8th annual legislative questionaire of Joe Holt.
    - EUROPA Booklets pamphlets listed alphabetically, 1957
      Americal association with Britain, Aujourd'hui a Paris, British Railway map,Danish silver, deckplan of s.s. Uniter States, Hamburg Chamber of Commerce annual report '56, Hamburg pamphlets, London weekly diary of socilal events, London: what to see,passengers lists ss United States, pictures of McDonough wife, places of interest London, SAS flight tickets Paris-Copenhagen,Scotland's north west highlands,Scottish Tourist Board, U S overseas information activities-libraries. U S Information Agency, USIS programs in Norway, France [UNK]
      Edinburgh map, menu's aboard, gala dinner, shopping in [UNK]
    - EUROPEAN TRIP, 1955
      - Austria-Vienna
        Austria's financial economic situation 2nd quarter '55 development of employment income in Italy 1955-1964, Export Import Bank of Washington- oustanding loans in Austria,Italy, Spain,Export-Import Bank credits to Austria, Austris's requirements for foreign capital, pictures, Russian evacuation of Austria,statistical data on Austria '54, statements of loans credits authorized by EXIM bank.
      - France-Paris
        French agriculture '55,economic revies of France '55 2nd quarter, facts figures USIS- American Embassy, facts sheets on France '54, Foreign Serice dispatches.
    - GERMANY Guide of Cologne cathedral, handbook ofe economis statistics, pa phlets [UNK], Bad Godesberg.
    - ITALY
      - Florence Naples Rome Venice
        Florece pamphlets, general report on economis situation of Italy in 1954, history of Florece handicrafts, instituto mobiliare italiano 1953 -balace sheests reports, Italian loan operations of EXIM bank, Italy-hints for American ITA, Naples program, pamphlets Naples Venice -maps, pictures McDonough wife, structure of Italian Banking system '55, tourists information.
    - ENGLAND
      - London
        American associations in Britain, hotels restaurants in London summary U K economic situation '55
    - BELGIUM
      Belgian Congo RUANDA - Urundi, economic resume Belgium '55, EXIM 19 semi-annual report to Congress July-Dec. 1954, facts on Belgium booklet, industrial investements in Belgium, investigations of EXIM bank loan activities '53, outline of Belgium for official visitors Amercan Embassy Brussels.
    - CONGRESSIONAL DISTRICT ATLAS of US Mapof L A county Districts, 1960
    - HOME LOAN GUARANTEE hold correspondance HR 10637, 1958
    - INGLEWOOD DAILY NEWS page II copies 80 Congress, 1947
    - MILITARY AIRCRAFT Correspondance 1960 Authorization for non military use surplus materials
    - MCDONOUGH PHOTO with Capitol nr I, factbook of Republican campaigners Billie Sol estates case., 1963
    - NEW BILL FORMS
    - TAFT HARTLEY LABOR BILL correspondance, 1947
    - Facts book for republican campaigners (Republican National Committee), 1962
  - MISCELLANEOUS C-T, 1954
    in manilla enveloppes folders with headings
    - California Campaign Office (Box 98)
    - Campaign (Press releases data) enveloppe
    - Campaign Material (campaign 1sts)
    - Campaign Material (postal zones, precints, clippings, vote tabulations, primary campaign)
    - Catholic Directory
    - Congratulations (letters)
    - Congratulations (letters) in enveloppe
    - Census Data in enveloppe
    - Census Data in folder
    - No-Bricker (Bricker amendment)
    - Official tabulations IBM on election vote November
    - Petition signers (letters)
    - Political campaign (letters pamphlets), July- '54
    - Political campaign in enveloppe
    - Publicity-Election (letters newspaper clippings)
    - Signers for McDonough for re-election to Congr, list of signers)
    - Thanks for support (letters)
  - MISCELLANEOUS, C-W, 1954-1962
    - Campaign (folder enveloppe), 1956 (Box 99)
    - Challenge list compiled from returns of precincts sheets mailing, 85 Congr. district., June 1956
    - Election Publicity (newspaper clippings, letters Kick off Program), 1956
    - Election letters sent to MCDonough, 1956
    - Emory S Petty campaign, 1956
    - National Republican Convention tickets, 1956
    - Nomination petitons for McDonough Petty (lists of signers)
    - Opinion polls (tabulations), 1962
    - Photo's of McDonough a. o.
    - Questinaires, 1959
    - Republican File, 1954, '55 '56
    - Signers for McDonough re-election to Congress, 1956
    - Statement of articles used by McDonough in campaign, 1956
    - Ticket requests for National Republican Convention, 1956
    - Washington Report (changes removal from mailing lists), 1957-'58
    - BOOKLET:
      - Major legislative action 87 Congress, 1962
  - MISCELLANEOUS,I-V, 1956-1959
    arr. alphabetically by HEADINGSI
    - INTERPARLIAMTARY UNION CONFERENCE, WARSHAW, 1959 (Box 100)
      Constitutional parlamentary preliminary documents, constitution regulations of th DIET people's Council Act, information 1959, listings of delegates, interparlamentiary bulletin '59, World Affairs issue winter '59.
    - INTERPARLIAMENTARY UNION U S A
      Agenda papers, agenda papers (see folder for subjects), Assembly of Captive European Nations, constitutional parlamentary information '57, control reductions of arms report, Cremer W R union personality, draft resolutions, Houses of Parliament- illustrated guide, inter parliamentary bulletin '57, inter parliamentary information handbook '57, interparliamentary 46th union conference London '57, international finance corporation annual report '57, London reception corporation, lists of delegates, opening ceremony by Queen, preliminary documents of conference, Polish government in exile, pictures of delegates, Queen's speech at opening, refugee problem, speeches messages, summary reports 4 5 8 10, visit to royal naval college.
      Address by Arch bishop of Savanah, by Lord bishop of London, on: stabilization of prices for primary products, address by Queen Prime Minister Mc Millan.
    - MOSCOW -RUSSIA PERSONAL, Sept. 1959
      American exhibitions, Ford motor Co. Pan-am russian brochures maps of Moscow, Moscow -Leningrad -Kiew pamphlets, pictures, Polish news bulletin of American British embassies Warshaw. press bulletin of U S ambassy Warshaw, travel in the USSR booklet, travel schedules.
    - McDONOUGH PERSONAL FOLDERS [UNK] removed from file, 1956
      Banking currency committee, campain workers 1948 list, endorsements re-elections 1952, Fuelton Lewis Poll-votectabulations, government operations committee 1953 '54, housing 82 Congr., legislative calendar 1954 83 Congr. 1st 2nd sessions, public law 455 547 HR 7072 8370.
    - A C A INDEX Analyses of voting records of members of Congress
    - CONGRESSIONAL RECORD Digest tally of Roll call votes, 1961
    - FREE CITIZENS VOTING RECORD 86 Congress 1st Session, 1959
    - FREE CITIZENS VOTING RECORD 86 Congress 1st Session California, 1959
    - McDonough VOTING RECORD 80 Congress 1st Session
    - McDonough VOTING RECORD, 1951-1953
    - MAJOR LEGISLATIVE ACTION 81 Congress 1st Session
    - MAP of City of SAN CLEMENTE, 1951
    - PRESIDENTIAL APPOINTRMENTS key goverment personell, 1961
    - PUBLIC GENERAL BILLS RELATED
    - RESOLUTIONS with index
      Digest of.. 87 Congress 1st Session
    - VOTING RECORD MC DONOUGH
      HOUSE 1945 '58 61 alphabetically chronologically by subject.
    - VOTING RECORD MC DONOUGH 81 Congress, Jan 1949- June 30 1950
    - VOTING RECORD MC DONOUGH 79 Congress 1st Session
    - VOTING RECORD MC DONOUGH 79 Congress 2nd Session, 1946
  - MISCELLANEOUS, C-F, 1957-1959
    in manilla enveloppes folders with headings arr. alphabetically by HEADINGS
    - California delegation (letters) (Box 101)
    - California Republican delegation (letters)
    - Campaign, 1958
    - Campaign
    - Endorsements (letters)
    - Inaugural Festical
    - Inaugural proceedings papers (Ball, banquets, Eisenhower- Nixon)
    - Material from Virginia's desk (voting lists, precint workers)
    - November Elections (newspaper clippings)
    - November Elections (newspaper letters)
    - Five Star Flag
  - MISCELLANEOUS, B-U, 1945-1962
    in folders enveloppes
    - Baby book list (labels) (Box 102)
    - Bills introduced by Mc Donough 85 Congr., 1957
    - Cohen, Marvin, 1951-54
    - Congratulations on re-election, Nov. '52
    - Labor file for corrective legisl. 80 Congr. HR 3020, 1947
    - Labor legislation, papers for... 80 Congr., 1947
    - Legislatif political record McDonough, 1933-1962
    - Miscellaneous materials (lists volunteer campain workers a. o.), 1956
    - McDonough Column, 1953
    - McDonough # Said done in Washington, 1953
    - McDonough # Said done in Washington, Jan. 1954- May 1954
    - New Bill material for 83 Congr.1952 HR 7448 RS 4426 S, 1286
    - News letters, 1957 '58
    - Nut industry, 1945-'46
    - Regret letters (lost election), 1962
    - Republican Organizations 15 Congr. district, 1953
    - Roll call analyses, 1950
    - Unmarked folder H J RES 325
- Washington Report
  In folders enveloppes
  Arr. by YEAR
  - Washington Report, Jan- 1955 (Box Box W R 15)
  - Washington Report, June-1955
  - Washington Report, Master file 1955
  - Washington Report, 1956
  - Washington Report, 1957
  - Washington Report, 1958
  - Washington Report, 1959
  - Washington Report, May 1959
  - Washington Report, June 1955
  - Washington Report General, 1959, '60
  - Washington Report, August 1960
  - Washington Report, Special 1960
  - Washington Report, 1960
  - Washington Report, 1961
  - Washington Report, 1961
  - Washington Report list, 1961
  - Washington Report, 1962
  - Washington Report, 1962
  - Washington Report Opinion Poll, 1962
  - Washington Report Correspondance, 1962
  - Washington Report McDonough views on various bills (see folder) F B I file opening, Girard case, Inter-Parliamentary Union 46 Congress, list of congressional [UNK] legislations, lists of major bills introduced [UNK] McDonogh, [UNK] pracice of Communism, reduce budget taxes, H Res 170,[UNK] of Forces Agreement H J Res 61, list of appropriation bills reduced., 1956 1956-1957-1958
  - Washington Report Letters answered.
  - Washington Report Lists of names added to W R list Hollywood Industrial Guide lists of precinct workers., lists of 85 86 Assembly distric persons.
    extracted from correspondance.
  - Washington Report Master file poll results, 1956
  - Washington Report Replies to questionnaire W R HR 9150 H J Res 523, 1959 '60
- FAVOR file
  Belonging to the McDonough collection are 3 boxes (103 thr. 105) marked Favor file.
  Boxes contain letters in folders not in an alphabetical or chronological arrangement Box contents are arranged chronologically by [UNK]
  - FAVOR file, 1945/1950
    correspondance in folders with heading
    box arrangement of folders: chronological
    correspondance in folders not strictly confined to time period of heading
    letters in folders not structly in alpahetical or chronological arrangement
    - FAVOR, 1946 (Box 103)
    - FAVOR MISCELLANEOUS, 1945
    - FAVOR (PERSONAL), 1945
    - FAVOR, January 1947
    - FAVOR, May 1947
    - FAVOR, August 1947
    - FAVOR, October 1947
    - FAVOR, January thr.July 1948
    - FAVOR, November 1948
    - FAVOR, December 1948
    - FAVOR, January thr. December 1949
    - FAVOR FORMLETTER
    - FAVOR, January thr. December 1950
    - FAVOR, August September October 1948
  - FAVOR file, 1951/1956
    letters in folders not strictly in alphabetical or chronological arrangement
    - 1951 January thr. December (Box 104)
    - 1952 January thr. July
    - 1953 January thr. July
    - 1954 January thr. July
    - 1955 January thr. July
    - 1956 January thr. May
  - FAVOR file, 1957/1961
    - January 1957 (Box 105)
    - May 1957
    - January 1958
    - July 1958
    - January 1959
    - May 1959
    - January 1960
    - May 1960
    - January 1961
    - May 1961
    - Favor White House tour, 1959
    - Favor White House tour, 1960
    - Favor cases, January 1959
- SUPPLEMENT listing of materials in FILING CABINET
  Materials in folders enveloppes
  Box arr. alphabetically numerical by Congress distrit zones
  T list copies not seperated
  Also in drawer: car license plates (special: D C)
  - Tee list 30 District carbon copy, 5 (Draw Draw 1)
  - Tee list 30 Originals, 5
  - Tee list original copies (3), 12
  - Tee list original copies, 13
  - Tee list original copies (3), 14
  - Tee list original copies (3), 15
  - Tee list original copies (3), 16
  - Tee list original copies (3), 17 18
  - Tee list original C I, 19
  - Tee list originals, 19
  - Tee list originals copies (3), 21 list seperated
  - Tee list Virginia all copies (3), 23
  - Tee list originals Copies (2), 26
  - Tee list originals Copies, 28
  - Tee list originals Copies (3), 31
  - Tee list originals Copies, 33
  - Tee list Virginia all copies (3), 36
  - Tee list originals copies, 38
  - Tee list originals (2), 57
  - California Newspaper Directory, 1962/'63
  - Campaign letters, 1954
  - Colonel John Glenn USMC
  - Completedlists, 1960
  - Contributions campaign, 1962
  - Correspondance, 1962
  - General bills (HR 's) (HR 471-12319, 48 bills)
  - Mc Donough election returns, 1944/'62
  - Mc Donough photo with Capitol nr I nr 2
  - Merchant Marine
  - Miscellaneous, 1962
  - Negatives of 30Th District maps
  - Photo albums
  - Protestant ministers prayer ban labels
  - Rep. Mc Donough please call me, Lee Walch
  - Replies to March 6 letters, 1962
  - 30Th District cessus data traxts ways
  - Various photo's
  - Campaign, 1950 (Draw Draw 2)
  - Frank P O Sullivan, 1954
  - Gordon M Mc Donough, Jr. Campaign Campaign for council 5th District, L A
  - Harry W Flannery election, 1950
  - Personal, January 1952 '54
  - Personal Correspondance
  - Personal Political, April 1953
  - Personal Political, Sept. '48
  - Personal Political, June '49
  - Personal Political, Jan. '51
  - Personal Political, July '52
  - Political Campaign, 1953
  - Election, 1944
  - Election, 1946
  - Election-returns, 1948
  - Election, 1950